Hello and welcome, I'm Mariam and thank you
for taking the time to visit my website.
For the past two years, I've been working in
the iGaming industry as a game show host.
Every day I communicate with hundreds of players
from different countries — adapting quickly to
new situations and making sure every
interaction is a positive one.
As I started thinking about the next step in
my career, I also invested my time in
developing new skills by completing customer
support courses, including Intercom and
Zendesk. I'm always looking for
opportunities to learn and grow.
Now I'm excited to move into customer support,
customer success, operations, or player experience.
I enjoy working with people, solving problems
and being part of a team, and I would
love to continue building my career
in the iGaming industry.
Feel free to explore my website to learn
more about my experience, skills and
certifications. Thank you for watching —
I look forward to connecting with you.